vitaminwater.com 2019-12-25

# Privacy Policy

We, The Coca-Cola Company and its affiliates, take our consumers’ privacy seriously.  Our mission is to refresh the world and we can’t do that without your trust. This Privacy Policy explains what information we collect about you, why we collect the information, as well as how we collect and use the information so that we can deliver the best, most refreshing experience that we can. 

This Privacy Policy is intended for individuals in the United States. If you live outside of the United States and choose to use the Sites connected with this Privacy Policy, you do so at your own risk and understand that your information will be sent to and stored in the United States. By using any of our websites and mobile applications in the United States (collectively, “Sites”) or otherwise providing Personal Information to us, you agree to this Privacy Policy. 

**PERSONAL INFORMATION**

“ **Personal Information** ” generally means any information that identifies you as an individual, and any other information we associate with it.  We collect a few categories of information, from a few different sources:

1\. Profile information and other content you voluntarily provide us, which may include:

  * User name and password
  * Contact information when you register on our Sites, such as your name, street address, demographic information (such as your gender), date of birth, phone number, and/or email address. You may also provide us information about other people, such as when you direct us to send a gift on your behalf.
  * Any content or contributions you post in a public space on the Sites. This includes comments, videos and photos that you might submit. If you contact us through a social media site, we may collect your social media identifier.
  * Any information you provide in communications with us, such as via social media, e-mail or our customer call center.
  * Payment information, such as when you make a purchase with us and we need your billing information to process the transaction.

2. Information that is passively collected when you use the Sites, such as by our web servers and by third party analytics tools we use:

  * Our system logs may record certain information about visitors to our Sites, including the web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device and mobile ad identifiers, browser information, interaction with the Sites, pages viewed, app usage, and other such information; we may collect similar information from emails you receive from us that can help us track which emails are opened and which links are clicked by recipients.
  * We use certain cookies, pixel tags and other technologies to help us understand how you use the Sites and enable us to personalize your experience.  To learn more about cookies, please visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org/.](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)  To learn more about Coca-Cola’s use of cookies, please see our cookie policy.  We may ask advertisers or other third party partners to serve ads or services to your devices, which rely on cookies or similar technologies placed on our Sites.
  * We may detect the physical location of your device by, for example, using GPS information collected by mobile apps or location information shared by your web browser.  We collect this information for purposes of enhancing or facilitating our services, such as enabling certain functionalities of the Sites that can provide you with information about promotions or relevant product information near you. We may use your device’s physical location to better understand how our Sites and other services and functionality are being used and to provide you with relevant and personalized location-based services and content, including advertising. Should you wish to opt out of the collection of this information, please adjust the settings of your device so that information about your physical location is not sent to us or third parties by (a) disabling location services within the device settings; or (b) denying certain websites or mobile applications permission to access location information by changing the relevant preferences and permissions in your mobile device or browser settings. Please note that your location may be derived from your WiFi, Bluetooth, and other device settings. Please consult your device settings for further information.

3\. We may receive information from third parties such as advertising and marketing partners, public databases, and social media platforms, to supplement the information we receive from our consumers. If we do so, this policy governs how we can use that information.

4\. In addition to collecting Personal Information, we may collect information that does not identify you and is not associated with your Personal Information.  We may also de-identify information so it no longer identifies you.  We can aggregate and use such information to engage in marketing and other activities in a manner that protects our consumers since it does not use their Personal Information and is outside the scope of this Privacy Policy.

**How We May Use Personal Information**

We may use Personal Information as permitted by law, for the following business purposes:

  * to respond to your inquiries and fulfill your requests
  * to send administrative information to you, such as about your account or purchases or respond to your inquiries and requests for information
  * to communicate with you about orders, purchases, returns, services, donations, promotions, campaigns, programs, contests, sweepstakes, and accounts
  * to inform you about our brands, products, promotions, events or other promotional purposes
  * to re-contact you if we have not heard from you in a while
  * to send you advertising/promotional material from any of our affiliates, and on behalf of our promotional and strategic partners
  * to improve your experience with our products and services, such as by personalizing your experience with us
  * to process rewards, prizes, and donations, as applicable
  * to allow you to participate in polls, sweepstakes, instant win promotions, contests and other promotions and to administer these activities
  * to deliver gift cards or gifts to others in accordance with your instructions
  * to permit you to participate in social sharing, including live social media feeds
  * to perform analytics, quality control, market research, and determine the effectiveness of our websites, mobile applications, promotional campaigns, and develop new products and services

We may also use Personal Information as we believe to be necessary or appropriate for certain essential purposes, including:

  * to comply with applicable law and legal process
  * to respond to requests from public and government authorities, including public and government authorities outside your country of residence
  * to detect, prevent, or investigate potential security incidents or fraud
  * to facilitate the functionality of our mobile applications and websites
  * to provide important product safety information and notice of product recalls
  * to enforce our terms and conditions
  * to protect our operations or those of our affiliates
  * to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, security and/or that of our affiliates, you or others
  * to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain

If you submit any Personal Information relating to other people in connection with the Sites, you represent that you have the authority to do so and to permit us to use the information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**How Personal Information May Be Disclosed**

1\. To the extent permitted by law, all of your Personal Information may be disclosed with the following categories of third parties:

  * to our affiliates for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy
  * to our third-party service providers who provide services such as website hosting, data analysis, payment processing, order fulfillment, infrastructure provision, IT services, customer service, email delivery services, credit card processing, auditing services and other services, to enable them to provide services
  * to a third party in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets or stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings)
  * in connection with the essential purposes described above (e.g., to comply with legal obligations)

2. To the extent permitted by law, your name and contact information (and other information you make public) may be disclosed with the following categories of third parties:

  * to third-party strategic partners with whom we may enter into a special relationship for promotional activities, where permitted by law
  * to third parties in connection with certain promotions or sweepstakes you may participate in; to the extent that the promotion’s rules concerning the treatment of your Personal Information are stricter than this Privacy Policy, the promotion’s rules apply

3. To the extent permitted by law, information that is passively collected when you use the Sites may be disclosed with the following categories of third parties:

  * our online and email advertisers or other third-party vendors we use who may provide cookies, pixel tags, web beacons, clear GIFs or other similar technologies for use on our Sites or other websites to manage and improve our online and email advertising campaigns.

For example, a vendor (e.g., Google, Facebook) may provide us with certain digital advertising pixels or other tools to recognize their cookies during your visit to the Sites and to learn which of our online advertisements may have brought you to our Sites, or to serve you with advertisements for Coca-Cola products after you leave the Sites.  These third-party vendors may also use other digital advertising tools, as well as your Personal Information, to recognize you across the devices and online services you use.  To learn more about Coca-Cola’s use of cookies, please see our cookie policy.

**DO NOT TRACK**

We do not monitor or follow “Do Not Track” (DNT) signals because there is no standard interpretation or practice for DNT signals. Therefore, we handle all user information consistent with this Privacy Policy.

**THIRD PARTY SITES**

The Sites may link to other web sites and online services.  We have no control over such third parties and therefore cannot be responsible for the content, availability, or security of such linked third-party websites, so please read their privacy policies carefully. Third parties may use your information for their own purposes, including behavioral or advertising purposes. This Privacy Policy does not address the privacy and data security practices of any third parties.  The inclusion of a link on the Sites does not imply endorsement of the linked third-party website or their products and services, and is provided for your convenience only.  If you decide to access any of the third-party websites linked to our Sites, you do so subject to the terms and conditions of use for such third-party websites.

This Privacy Policy only applies to Coca-Cola Sites that contain a link to this Privacy Policy.  There may be other websites that reference the Coca-Cola brand but are subject to different terms.

We are also not responsible for the privacy and data security practices of other organizations, such as Facebook, Instagram, Apple, Google, Microsoft, Twitter or any other app developer, app provider, social media platform provider, operating system provider, wireless service provider or device manufacturer.  Please read their privacy policies and consider customized settings on your browser or through your mobile phone to limit disclosure of certain information, such as location data.

Any Personal Information that you provide through these third-party websites, mobile applications, or social platforms will be subject to the privacy policy of the its operator, and not this Privacy Policy.

**CAREERS**

The Sites may include a link to our Careers section. Any Personal Information submitted through that portion of the Sites, by upload or via e-mail, will be governed by our Resume/CV Submission Policy at <http://www.coca-colacompany.com/careers/>.

**SECURITY**

We use standard physical, technical and administrative measures designed to reduce the risk of loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of your Personal Information. Unfortunately, no system or network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.  If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure (for example, if you feel that the security of any account you might have with us has been compromised), please immediately notify us in accordance with the _“Contacting Us”_ section below (note that physical mail notification will delay the time it takes for us to respond to the problem).

**YOUR CHOICES AND ACCESS RIGHTS**

**Your choices regarding our use and disclosure of your Personal Information**

  * You can opt out of receiving promotional emails and mailing by informing us of your preferences when you sign up for a Coca-Cola account or modifying your promotional preferences online in your profile account management section. To stop receiving phone, mail, SMS, and/or email marketing communications from us, you may text “STOP” to a text message from us or click “unsubscribe” at the bottom of an email from us. In addition, you may let us know as directed below in the _“Contacting Us”_ section.  Please specify which types of communications you no longer wish to receive, and the relevant telephone number, address, and/or e-mail address.  If you do opt-out of receiving marketing-related messages from us, we may still send you important administrative messages, such as emails about your accounts or purchases.
  * We will not disclose your Personal Information to third parties if we have received and processed a request from you not to do so. To submit such a request, please contact us by clicking here: _Do Not Sell My Personal Information_.  Please note that we may continue to share your Personal Information with our affiliates, service providers, for essential purposes described above and other such circumstances.  

**How you can access or delete your Personal Information**

  * You may request a copy of the following:  (1) The categories of Personal Information we collected about you; (2) The categories of sources from which the Personal Information is collected; (3) The business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling (if applicable) the Personal Information; (4) The categories of third parties with whom we share Personal Information; and (5) The specific pieces of Personal Information we have collected about you.
  * You may request that we delete your personal information.  Note that deletion requests are subject to certain limitations, for example, we may retain Personal Information as permitted by law, such as for tax or other record keeping purposes, to maintain an active account, and to process transactions and facilitate customer requests.

You have the right not to be discriminated against in service or price if you exercise your privacy rights, and we will love you just as much if you do exercise them.

To request a copy of Personal Information we have collected about you, or to request that the your information be deleted, please contact us by clicking here: _Privacy Requests_.  You may authorize another person (your “agent”) to submit a request on your behalf.  If an authorized agent will be submitting a request for you, please contact us at [privacy@coca-cola.com](mailto:privacy@coca-cola.com). We will aim to complete requests as soon as reasonably practicable and consistent with any applicable laws. Please note that we are required to verify that your agent has been properly authorized to request information on your behalf and this may take additional time to fulfill your request.

If you have an account with us, you may also make certain changes directly through your account profile page. Please note that changes you make on your account profile page through one of our Sites may not always be reflected on other Sites operated by us.

**RETENTION PERIOD**

We will retain your Personal Information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by for legal, auditing, or compliance purposes.

**CHILDREN'S PRIVACY**

We do not intend for our websites or other online services to knowingly collect or solicit any information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow minors under the age of 13 to disclose their Personal Information to us through the Sites.  The Sites are directed to individuals who are permitted to share their Personal Information without parental consent.  If you believe that we might have any information from a child under 13, please contact us as directed below in the _“Contacting Us”_ section. You may mark your inquiry “COPPA Information Request.” Parents can learn more about how to protect children’s privacy online [here](https://www.consumer.ftc.gov/articles/0031-protecting-your-childs-privacy-online).

We may ask for additional consent during the account sign-up process from minors ages 13 to 15 years of age under relevant and applicable laws if personal information may be shared outside of Coca-Cola and its affiliates and service providers.

If you are under the age of 18 and a registered user of the Sites, you may ask us to remove content or information that you have posted to the Sites by contacting us as directed below in the _“Contacting Us”_ section. Please note that your request does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content or information, for example, another user of the Sites may have reposted your public content somewhere else on the Sites or on another website.

**UPDATES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We may periodically update this Privacy Policy.  Please reference the “ _LAST UPDATED_ ” legend at the top of this page to see when this Privacy Policy was last revised.  Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective when we post the revised Privacy Policy on our Sites.  Your use of the Sites following these changes means that you accept the revised Privacy Policy.

**CONTACTING US**

We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our data practices, please contact us as follows:

1.   You may email us at: [https:/us.coca-cola.com/help/](https://us.coca-cola.com/help/)

2.   You may call us at 1-800-438-2653

Please note that email communications are not always secure, so please do not include credit card information or other sensitive information in any emails to us.

When you use our websites, mobile applications, and online services (the “Site”), we may store cookies on your web browser.  Other third parties you choose to visit may do the same.  This Cookie Policy explains what a cookie is, how you can manage your cookies, and what kind of cookies may be on our sites.

**1\. WHAT IS A COOKIE AND WHY DO WE USE THEM?**

Cookies are small pieces of text.  They are provided by most websites and stored by your web browser on the computer, phone, or other device that you are using.  Cookies serve many purposes.  They can help a website remember your preferences, learn which areas of the website are useful and which areas need improvement, and provide you with targeted advertisements or personalized content.  Sometimes, cookies are enabled when pixels are placed on a website. Pixels are also referred to as web beacons, clear gifs, and tags. They enable websites to read and place cookies. 

**First-party cookies and third-party cookies**

Cookies can be first-party or third-party.  A first-party cookie is one that you receive directly from The Coca-Cola Company when visiting our Site.  A third-party cookie is one that you have received from another party, such as Google or Facebook.  We do not control what third parties do on other sites.  However, we may work with certain third-party providers such as Google or Facebook to permit their cookies to function through our Site so we can learn more about your web experience on our Site and better personalize our services for you.

**Persistent and session cookies**

A persistent cookie is a cookie that is stored by the web browser on your device until it expires or you delete it. The expiration of a persistent cookie is determined by the creator of the cookie and can be upon a certain date or after a length of session time has passed. This means that, for the cookie's entire lifespan, its information will be transmitted to the creator’s server every time the user visits the website that it belongs to or another website configured to check for that cookie (such as an advertisement placed on that website). For this reason, persistent cookies are also called “tracking cookies.”

A session cookie is created temporarily on your device for use by a website during your visit. This type of cookie may store information you enter and track your activity within the website. A session cookie is deleted after you leave the website or when the web browser is closed.  A good example of a session cookie is the shopping cart on an e-commerce site. The session cookie stores the items that you add to your cart so they are not forgotten while you view products on other pages of the website. Using a session cookie, the items will all be in the cart when you go to the checkout page.

**2\. HOW DO I MANAGE COOKIES?**

Most web browsers let you choose whether to accept cookies.  Most also let you delete cookies already set.  The choices available, and the mechanism used, will vary from browser to browser.  Such browser settings are typically found in the “options”, “tools” or “preferences” menu. You may also consult the browser’s “help” menu. For example: 

There are online tools available for clearing all cookies left behind by the websites you have visited, such as [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).  Usually, deletion of cookies will anonymize the information associated with the pixel and a website will not receive any further associated information.

**3\. WHAT KIND OF COOKIES DO WE USE?**

The Site may use Strictly Necessary Cookies, Performance Cookies, Functional Cookies, Targeting Cookies and Social Media Cookies.  Any of these may be first-party cookies or third-party cookies, persistent or session. Please reference Section 2 of this Cookie Policy for information on how to manage these cookies through your browser.

  * **Strictly Necessary Cookies:**   These are cookies without which you would not be able to use this Site. For example, Strictly Necessary Cookies adjust the Site data transmitted to match your Internet connection, get you to the secure versions of the Site, and help provide services you specifically request.  If you set your browser to block these cookies, some parts of the Site will not work. Strictly Necessary Cookies do not store any Personal Information.
  * **Performance Cookies:** We use these cookies to count visits and traffic sources, to measure and improve Site performance. They help us to know which pages are the most and least popular and see how visitors move around the site.  Performance Cookies do not store any Personal Information.
  * **Functional cookies:** These cookies allow the Site to remember choices you make and provide enhanced functionality and more personalized features.  Depending on context, Functional Cookies may store certain types of Personal Information as needed to provide functionality.
  * **Targeting Cookies:**  Targeting cookies help us manage and display our advertisements, based on your activity on the Site and other sites; this is known as interest-based advertising.  Targeting cookies mainly rely on uniquely identifying your browser and internet device. We have partnered with the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) to better serve users’ preferences, and by visiting their website at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>, you can learn more about NAI members who deliver tailored online ads and your choices to opt-out of receiving them. Opting out of interest-based advertising does not mean you will no longer see advertising online, but it does mean that the companies from which you opt out will no longer show ads that have been tailored to your interests.
  * **Social Media Cookies:**   Social Media Cookies make social sharing easier for you, provide you with tools to connect with the Site, and help us better understand both the audience for the Site and the effectiveness of our social media outreach.  These are third-party cookies.  Your choices with respect to such cookies are determined by the social media platforms on which you have accounts.

**4.   UPDATES TO THIS COOKIE POLICY**

We may change this Cookie Policy at any time.  Please review the “LAST UPDATED” legend at the top of this page to see the last revision date to this Cookie Policy.  Any changes in this Cookie Policy will become effective when the revised Cookie Policy is available on or through the Site.

**5.   CONTACTING US**

If you have any further questions, please contact us by calling us at 1-800-438-2653

At Coca-Cola, we take your privacy very seriously, and **we never monetize your information** ; we use it to enhance your experience with opportunities like special promotions and nearby offers.

When it comes to your rights as a consumer, we want to make sure you have everything you need to make informed decisions. You have the right to:

  * Know how your personal information is used;
  * Access, request and receive the personal information we have collected in a portable manner;
  * Object to having your data sold or shared;
  * And request that we delete your personal data.

Soon you’ll be able to make requests about your privacy rights. In in the interim, please tap CONTACT US below to reach out to a Coca-Cola representative or get answers to frequently asked questions.
